(Sheldon:)...here I am.
(Penny:)You just walked in
and they hired you?
(Penny:)-Just like that?
-Oh, heavens no.
(Sheldon:)Since I don't need to be paid,
I didn't need to be hired.
(Sheldon:)I simply came in, picked up a tray
and started working for the man.
(Sheldon:)Let me get that plate out of your way.
(Penny:)Sheldon, this is ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)Is it? Just a moment ago,
I had a minor epiphany...
...regarding polymer degradation
phenomenon...
(Sheldon:)...while scraping congealed nachos
off a plate.
(Sheldon:)-Bernadette, table 10 wants their check.
-Thanks.
(Penny:)Sheldon, wait. This isn't even what I do.
I'm a waitress, not a busboy.
(Sheldon:)You're right. That is more menial.
(Sheldon:)Hello, I'm Sheldon.
I'll be your server today.
(Sheldon:)I don't recommend the salmon.
(Sheldon:)I saw it in the kitchen.
(Sheldon:)All right. One bacon cheeseburger...
(Sheldon:)...breaking two Jewish
dietary restrictions simultaneously.
(Sheldon:)Kudos.
And beer-battered fish and chips.